{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["that", "to", "search", "After"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["wagon", "in", "a", "search"]}, {"explanation": "idea is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the _____________ of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lion", "tree", "wagon", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tickled", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tickled", "lion", "and", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "him", "The", "of"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["wagon", "mouse", "search", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "go is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["let", "take", "help", "go"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["to", "a", "a", "later"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went _____________ search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "of", "in", "after"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["the", "idea", "was", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: wagon", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["of", "take", "they", "wagon"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["tree", "mouse", "search", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search _____________ a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["in", "of", "after", "by"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: being", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (present participle).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["being", "go", "lion", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to _____________ him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["go", "take", "let", "help"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["after", "by", "in", "that"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: hunters", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["to", "tree", "hunters", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: captured", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past participle).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tree", "later", "captured", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: let", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["so", "The", "by", "let"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Select appropiate Adverb from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["later", "Sometime", "sometime", "so"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: Sometime", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["to", "a", "Sometime", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: went", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["a", "in", "After", "went"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["After", "of", "that", "in"]}], "success": 1}